beaches.com 2011-06-02

# Privacy Policy for Beaches All-Inclusive Caribbean Vacation

Privacy Statement  
This privacy statement covers the Sandals.com and Beaches.com websites. Because these web sites want to demonstrate their commitment to our users' privacy, they have agreed to disclose their information practices and their privacy practices.

Information Collection  
Unique Vacations, Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on Sandals.com and Beaches.com. Unique Vacations, Inc., as the worldwide representative for Sandals and Beaches, collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site. Unique Vacations, Inc. provides a number of ways for visitors/customers to 'opt-out' of receiving additional information from us. These are offered at the time visitors/customers provide us their information, when they receive an e-correspondence and/or by sending a written inquiry to Unique Vacations, Inc., 4950 S.W. 72 Ave., Miami, FL 33155. If visitors/customers do not wish to continue receiving any online promotional communications from Unique Vacations, Inc, such as e-mail or online newsletters, they can opt-out of receiving these communications by clicking on the unsubscribe link located on the bottom of the e-correspondence received.

Brochure Request and Booking Engine  
We request information from the user on our brochure request forms and in our booking engines. A user must provide contact information (such as name, email, and mailing address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes. If we have trouble processing an order, the information is used to contact the user.

Profile  
We store information that we collect through cookies and log files to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that details their viewing preferences. Consequently, collected information is tied to the users' personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the site for the user. This profile is used to tailor a user's visit to our Web site, and to direct pertinent marketing promotions to them. We do not share, under any circumstances, your profile with other third parties.

Cookies  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions.

Customer Service  
We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email or phone, in accordance with the users wishes.
